https://bosworthspindles.com/privacy-policy-2/

Privacy Policy
This Privacy Policy describes how your personal information is collected, used, and shared when you visit or make a purchase from bosworthspindles.com (the “Site”).
PERSONAL INFORMATION WE COLLECT
When you visit the Site, we automatically collect certain information about your device, including information about your web browser, IP address, time zone, and some of the cookies that are installed on your device. Additionally, as you browse the Site, we collect information about the individual web pages or products that you view, what websites or search terms referred you to the Site, and information about how you interact with the Site. We refer to this automatically-collected information as “Device Information.”
We collect Device Information using the following technologies:
– “Cookies” are data files that are placed on your device or computer and often include an anonymous unique identifier. For more information about cookies, and how to disable cookies, visit http://www.allaboutcookies.org.– “Log files” track actions occurring on the Site, and collect data including your IP address, browser type, Internet service provider, referring/exit pages, and date/time stamps.– “Web beacons,” “tags,” and “pixels” are electronic files used to record information about how you browse the Site.
Additionally, when you make a purchase or attempt to make a purchase through the Site, we collect certain information from you, including your name, billing address, shipping address, payment information (including credit card numbers or PayPal Account info), email address, and phone number. We refer to this information as “Order Information.”
When we talk about “Personal Information” in this Privacy Policy, we are talking both about Device Information and Order Information.
HOW DO WE USE YOUR PERSONAL INFORMATION?
We use the Order Information that we collect generally to fulfill any orders placed through the Site (including processing your payment information, arranging for shipping, and providing you with invoices and/or order confirmations).
Additionally, we use this Order Information to:Communicate with you;Screen our orders for potential risk or fraud; andProvide you with information relating to our products or services.
We use the Device Information that we collect to help us screen for potential risk and fraud (in particular, your IP address), and more generally to improve and optimize our Site (for example, by generating analytics about how our customers browse and interact with the Site, and to assess the success of our marketing and advertising campaigns).
SHARING YOUR PERSONAL INFORMATION
We share your Personal Information with certain select third parties. For example, we share your personal information with our payment processor in order to process your payment. We also use Google Analytics to help us understand how our customers use the Site–you can read more about how Google uses your Personal Information here: https://www.google.com/intl/en/policies/privacy/. You can also opt-out of Google Analytics here: https://tools.google.com/dlpage/gaoptout.
We may also share your Personal Information to comply with applicable laws and regulations, to respond to a subpoena, search warrant or other lawful request for information we receive, or to otherwise protect our rights.
DO NOT TRACKPlease note that we do not alter our Site’s data collection and use practices when we see a Do Not Track signal from your browser.
YOUR RIGHTSIf you are a European resident, you have the right to access personal information we hold about you and to ask that your personal information be corrected, updated, or deleted. If you would like to exercise this right, please contact us through the contact information below.
Additionally, if you are a European resident we state that we are processing your information in order to fulfill contracts we might have with you (for example if you make an order through the Site), or otherwise to pursue our legitimate business interests listed above. Additionally, please note that your information will be transferred outside of Europe, including to Canada and the United States.
DATA RETENTIONWhen you place an order through the Site, we will maintain your Order Information for our records unless and until you ask us to delete this information.
CHANGESWe may update this privacy policy from time to time in order to reflect, for example, changes to our practices or for other operational, legal or regulatory reasons. This policy was last update on January 2, 2019.
CONTACT USFor more information about our privacy practices, if you have questions, or if you would like to make a complaint, please contact us by e-mail at sheilabb@bosworthspindles.com or by mail at:
Bosworth Spindles, 29 Main Street, Acton, MA, 01720, United States
Bosworth Spindles
Jonathan & Sheila Bosworth, Proprietors
29 Main StreetActon, MA 01720
© 2020 Bosworth Spindles | All rights reserved
Facebook
Twitter
Google-plus
Pinterest
This website uses cookies to improve your experience. Click "Got It!" to show you consent to this and dismiss this message.   Got It!   More InfoPrivacy & Cookies Policy
Close
Necessary
Necessary
Always Enabled
Journey Wheel is now
Bosworth Spindles.
Only the name has changed!
Please update your bookmarks.
Frequent Buyer Program
Every spindle you purchase in 2020 counts toward your 20% or 50% discount.
Purchase 4 spindles from us, and take a 20% discount on any size Standard spindle (available with hardwood shafts at surcharge)
OR
Purchase 5 spindles from us, and take 50% off any size Standard spindles (same offer for hardwood shafts).
PLUS, get a shipping credit of up to $10.25. This offer expires on December 31, 2020!
